Guide to the Ephemera collection, 1835-2002 MS2380
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ephemera, 1835-2002; Series 2
  - Howard Athenaeum, Howard Street., Circa [185-?]; Series 2; 1 broadside; 31 x 15 cm (Box 8, Folder 34)
    Subjects: Howard Athenaeum. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/no91006238; Howard Athenaeum. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00667076; Theaters Massachusetts Boston.; Theaters. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01149370; Massachusetts Boston. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01205012; Programs. rbgenr
  - 1877 D.C.: the year Washington became Washington., Circa 2002; Series 2; 52 pages: illustrations (some color), portraits; 27 cm (Box 8, Folder 35)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 400
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Special issue of the Washington post magazine commemorating the 125th anniversary of the Washington post, Dec. 8, 2002.; Out of the mud / by Tom Shroder -- Then and again: photographic evidence that no matter what anyone says about Washington, some things do change.
    Subjects: Washington post. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n84195638; Washington (D.C.) History. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145352; Washington (D.C.) Politics and government To 1878. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/subjects/sh85145357
  - Souvenir program of the President's Cup Regatta, Washington, D.C., September 7,8,14,15,20,21,22., Circa [1946]; Series 2; 12 unnumbered pages: illustrations, portraits; 31 cm (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 401
    Subjects: Regattas Washington (D.C.); Regattas. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01093037; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Programs. rbgenr
  - Program of the activities for the benefit of the National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis and to commemorate the birthday of its founder, Franklin D. Roosevelt, January 30, 1946., Circa [1946]; Series 2; 80 pages: illustrations, portraits; 28 cm e + 3 supplements (Box 8, Folder 37)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 402
    Cataloger notes: "Official program."; Supplements: Supplement to 1946 official program of Roosevelt Birthday celebration; Menu; Seating list.
    Subjects: Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 Anniversaries, etc.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00032031; National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n83001854; National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00577976; Fund raising Washington (D.C.); Anniversaries. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00809757; Fund raising. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00936143; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505; Programs. rbgenr
  - Washington Redskins -- 1937 world's champions., Circa [1937]; Series 2; 1 photographic print mounted on wood: black and white; 9 x 26 cm. (Box 8, Folder 38)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 403
    Cataloger notes: Photograph of a framed photograph. Show team members with signatures of each man. Includes list of all the players.; Separated from: Burleith Citizens Association records.
    Subjects: Washington Redskins (Football team) Pictorial works. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79113822; Washington Redskins (Football team) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00537382; Football teams Washington (D.C.) Pictorial works.; Football teams. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst00931446; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01204505; Pictorial works. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/fst01423874
  - 1965 inaugural concert., Circa [1965]; Series 2; 16 unnumbered pages: portraits; 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 404
    Cataloger notes: Cover title.; Souvenir program. Edited by M. Robert Rogers; designed and produced by Hubert Leckie in consultation with William Walton.
    Subjects: Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973 Inauguration.; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973 fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00048810; National Symphony Orchestra (Washington, D.C.) http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n83152520; National Symphony Orchestra (Washington, D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00586900; Concert programs Washington (D.C.); Concert programs. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00872991; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743; Washington (D.C.) fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01204505
  - The Inaugural Committee presents the program for the inauguration of Richard Milhous Nixon, 37th President of the United States, and Spiro Theodore Agnew, 39th Vice President of the United States, January 20, 1969., Series 2; [46] pages: illustrations, portraits; 28 cm (Box 8, Folder 40)
    Original catalog no EPHEMERA 405
    Cataloger notes: Cover title: Official inaugural program, January 20, 1969.
    Subjects: Agnew, Spiro T., 1918-1996. http://id.loc.gov/authorities/names/n79081960; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994 Inauguration.; Agnew, Spiro T., 1918-1996. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00039674; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/00031384; Inauguration. fast http://id.worldcat.org/fast/01198743